<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Wellcome to Bo Zhao&#39;s Homepage</title>
    <link>https://www.zhaobo.me/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Wellcome to Bo Zhao&#39;s Homepage</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    
	<atom:link href="https://www.zhaobo.me/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>https://www.zhaobo.me/posts/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.zhaobo.me/posts/about/</guid>
      <description>I&#39;m an applied AI researcher at BMO AI, based in Toronto, Canada. Prior to that, I worked at the University of British Columbia as a Postdoctoral Research Fellow with Prof. Leonid Sigal. I obtained my Ph.D. degree from Southwest Jiaotong University in 2017, supervised by Prof. Xiao Wu. I was also lucky to spend my last two years of my Ph.D. in the Learn­ing and Vi­sion Re­search Group at National University of Singapore as a visiting student with Prof.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Publications</title>
      <link>https://www.zhaobo.me/posts/publications/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://www.zhaobo.me/posts/publications/</guid>
      <description>DwNet: Dense Warp-based Network for Pose-guided Human Video Generation Polina Zablotskaia, Aliaksandr Siarohin, Leonid Sigal, Bo Zhao British Machine Vision Conference (BMVC), 2019 [arXiv]&amp;nbsp;[BibTex]      Image Generation from Layout Bo Zhao, Lili Meng, Weidong Yin, Leonid Sigal IEEE Conference on Computer Vision Pattern Recognition (CVPR), 2019 [arXiv]&amp;nbsp;[BibTex]      Where and when to look? Spatial-temporal attention for action recognition in videos Lili Meng, Bo Zhao, Bo Chang, Gao Huang, Frederick Tung, Leonid Sigal arXiv preprint, 2018 [arXiv]&amp;nbsp;[BibTex]      Modular Generative Adversarial Networks Bo Zhao, Bo Chang, Zequn Jie, Leonid Sigal European Conference on Computer Vision (ECCV), 2018 [arXiv]&amp;nbsp;[BibTex]      Multi-View Image Generation from a Single-View Bo Zhao, Xiao Wu, Zhi-Qi Cheng, Hao Liu, Zequn Jie, Jiashi Feng ACM Multimedia (MM), 2018 [Paper]&amp;nbsp;[BibTex]      Interpretable Multimodal Retrieval for Fashion Products Lizi Liao, Xiangnan He, Bo Zhao, Chong-Wah Ngo, Tat-Seng Chua ACM MM, 2018 [Paper]&amp;nbsp;[BibTex]      Left-Right Comparative Recurrent Model for Stereo Matching Zequn Jie, Pengfei Wang, Yonggen Ling, Bo Zhao, Yunchao Wei, Jiashi Feng, Wei Liu IEEE Conference on Computer Vision Pattern Recognition (CVPR), 2018 [arXiv]&amp;nbsp;[BibTex]      Sketch Recognition with Deep Visual-Sequential Fusion Model Jun-Yan He, Xiao Wu, Yu-Gang Jiang, Bo Zhao, Qiang Peng ACM Multimedia (MM), 2017 [Paper]&amp;nbsp;[BibTex]      Neural Person Search Machines Hao Liu, Jiashi Feng, Zequn Jie, Karlekar Jayashree, Bo Zhao, Meibin Qi, Jianguo Jiang, Shuicheng Yan International Conference on Computer Vision (ICCV), 2017 [arXiv]&amp;nbsp;[BibTex]      Memory-Augmented Attribute Manipulation Networks for Interactive Fashion Search Bo Zhao, Jiashi Feng, Xiao Wu, Shuicheng Yan IEEE Conference on Computer Vision Pattern Recognition (CVPR), 2017 [Paper]&amp;nbsp;[BibTex]      Diversified Visual Attention Networks for Fine-Grained Object Classification Bo Zhao, Xiao Wu, Jiashi Feng, Qiang Peng, Shuicheng Yan IEEE Transactions on Multimedia, 2016 (SCI, IF: 2.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>